<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joshua A. Welsh</title>
    <link>https://joadwe.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joshua A. Welsh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://joadwe.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://joadwe.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joadwe.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Joshua Welsh and I’m currently a Staff Scientist conducting research in Jennifer Jones’ lab within the ‘Laboratory of Pathology‘ at the National Cancer Institute in Bethesda, Maryland.
My main research interest is on small lipid spheres released from cells called extracellular vesicles (EVs). EVs contain proteins and genetic information from the cell they were released from. To date, I have investigated novel ways to detect and analyse EVs as well as their use as markers to diagnose and track the progression of disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>https://joadwe.github.io/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joadwe.github.io/code/</guid>
      <description>Output 1 % This is some example code 2 x = 1 3 4 5 6 7 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://joadwe.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joadwe.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>2023, MISEV, MIFlowCyt-EV, EV-TRACK: EV Reporting Standards, University College Dublin, Invited by Alfonso Blanco, PhD (Invited)
2023, Building Tools to Decipher Extracellular Vesicle Cargo, RoosterBio, Invited by Biji Mathew, PhD (Industry)
2023, Characterizing the unseen: The rise of small particle flow cytometry., CYTO2023, Invited by CYTO2023 IOC (Invited)
2022, Small Particles Flow Cytometry Analysis, 45th Annual Flow Cytometry Course, Invited by Lauren Nettenstrom, MS, SC​YM(ASCP) (Course)
2022, Developing tools for cross platform single EV analysis, Becton Dickinson, Invited by Aaron Tyznik, PhD (Industry)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://joadwe.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joadwe.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Welsh JA, Arkesteijn GJA, Bremer M, Cimorelli M, Dignat-George F, Giebel B, Görgens A, Hendrix A, Kuiper M, Lacroix R, Lannigan J, van Leeuwen TG, Lozano-Andrés E, Rao S, Robert S, de Rond L, Tang VA, Tertel T, Yan X, Wauben MHM, Nolan JP, Jones JC, Nieuwland R, van der Pol E., A compendium of single extracellular vesicle flow cytometry, J Extracell Vesicles. 2021 Dec;10(14):e12182. doi: 10.1002/jev2.12182., 2023, DOI: 10.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
